It's spring break!
You sure are cheerful, Miki.
Who wouldn't be? Look.
We're at a theme park!
Exams are over,
and spring break has begun.
What's a better way to spend it
than hanging out with friends?
This is what high school's about!
Hey, guys! Thanks for waiting.
There you are.
Heya, Minato and Yota.
Sorry, did we keep you waiting?
Nope.
Huh?
What's this, Minato?
Your outfit's on point today!
I've only seen you in casual outfits.
LIVE FEED - MINATO'S ROOM
MESSY
This is my casual fit.
- Well, shall we get going?
- Wait for me, Minato.
POWER WALKING
Let's go, Koyun.
Okay.
At Miki's suggestion,
the four of us came to the theme park.
EPISODE 10
SPRING
ENTRANCE
Glad it's a nice, warm day.
I love the feeling of the season changing.
I know what you mean.
MEMORIES TIED TO THE CLIMATE
It reminds me of the entrance ceremony.
MEMORIES - CLIMATE
It takes me back
to the day my younger siblings were born.
Were you and your siblings born in spring?
Yep, all April babies.
Koyun, your birthday's in February,
so you're almost a full year younger.
You're right.
February? That's pretty recent.
You should've told us.
Was I supposed to?
SHOCK
Excuse me. Can I get a birthday sticker?
Here you go.
But my birthday was last month--
STICK
Look over there.
PHOTO SHOOT OK!
ZONED OUT
The mascot looks bored.
Let's have it celebrate you.
Celebrate me?
And what's that thing supposed to be?
Don't be shy. Go, go, go.
Seriously, Yota... he's such a dad.
There.
- Dance with me.
- It's a bunny.
Uppi, uppi!
That's wacky.
- Someone help...
- Uppi!
SNAP, SNAP
I endorse this coupling.
Look, they're selling a ton of merch.
I'm kinda into this cheesy merch.
Cheesy?
UPPI BADGE SET
680 YEN (WITHOUT TAX)
- Thank you.
- Uppippi!
The mascot's the cashier?
I got some cute merch. Now I'm satisfied.
Hold on, what about the rides?
We haven't been on a single ride
since we got here.
No way! But we're having so much fun.
Then what if we go do that one?
HOUSE OF HORRORS
No!
Calm down, Miki.
It's just a prop. You're okay.
Koyun, no need to call it what it is.
I know what happens.
When we walk past the coffins,
the lids will swing open. I'm so done!
You'll be fine. Here, look.
HORROR
They put a lot of effort into this.
This is right up Tsukiko's alley.
This skull looks very realistic.
Right, Amamiya--
Don't look, don't look, don't look...
I can't even!
Take me away, Yota.
Sure. Yeah, okay.
CRASH
DROOP
ROUTE
Yota, that way to the exit.
EXIT
Moving on! On to the next one!
She's back to life.
Yay!
Yeah!
Yes!
Let's do this one together next.
It's their main attraction.
FAMOUS CYCLE MONORAIL
SCENIC VIEW
I'll pass.
UGH...
Sorry. I need a break.
Me too.
Guess all that spinning got to me.
Same here.
So...
sorry, but the two of you go on ahead.
THE TWO OF YOU
Koyun!
Looks like the wait time's much longer
than we thought, Yota.
Whoa, hey!
Watch your step!
Sorry.
It's fine.
How do I put it...
Yota's a bit...
The sea. It's glimmering!
I get a bit nervous if I look down.
He seems put together,
but he's actually pretty spacey.
He's like a big baby.
Miki and Yota,
they looked like a couple enjoying a date.
Huh? This situation's like...
BA-BUMP
It's as if we're on a date--
Amamiya.
Do you feel a bit sick today?
Are we pushing you too hard?
Not in the slightest.
I've felt great all day.
UPPI SAMBA
Yeah?
IN FACT, HE WAS EXCITED
SINCE YESTERDAY
I got a little queasy is all.
Huh... Then, maybe he's...
Hey. I wanna play that game while we wait.
Do you go to the arcade a lot?
Yeah, I like 'em.
Watch me.
He's a playful guy.
There!
Strike!
You got it on your first try.
We've got a winner!
Pick one prize from here.
UPPI
It's full of that mascot thing...
PRIZES
Now that's cute.
I'll take that one.
All right.
Amamiya has a real dog at home.
A REAL DOG
- We went off of my preference.
- Here.
PUFFY
You can have it.
Happy birthday, Koyun.
Huh? What?
NOT USED TO BEING CELEBRATED
What?
PUFFY - FLUFFY
FUZZY...
Thanks.
CLENCH
When's your birthday, Amamiya?
Will you do something for me?
SWOOSH
No, don't expect anything special...
There you are.
BAM
What the heck happened?
SEE YOU NEXT TIME
That was a blast.
Where do you wanna go for dinner?
I'll look up some places.
What kind of food?
STARE - PET, PET
- We walked a lot today.
- Say...
If I'm picking,
then I want to pile up on meat.
What is it?
Are you maybe...
not good with horror?
Right, Amamiya--
DEAD SILENT
AGAPE...
What? What gives you that idea?
Huh? Hold on.
How'd you know? Was it that obvious?
I mean...
I thought it'd be
something for little kids.
Man, this is embarrassing...
Maybe because his reaction
was contrary to my expectation...
Hey... Why're you looking at me like that?
Sorry, it's just...
"It's just..." what?
Wait up.
POWER WALKING
RUNNING AWAY - GIGGLE
- That's mean.
- She's fast.
For the first time in my life,
I thought a guy was cute.
NEW SEMESTER
GRADE 2, CLASS 2
Koyuki.
Good morning.
Tsukiko.
I'm glad we're in the same class again.
I'm looking forward
to being your classmate.
Me too.
Not many of the students in this class
are from Grade 1, Class 2.
I hardly recognize anyone.
I'm a bit nervous.
Do you know anyone?
Yeah, I see a few familiar faces...
Koyun.
Morning.
Morning, Yota.
How nice, you're so tall!
SHE ADMIRES TALL PEOPLE
- I know exactly how you feel.
- Wait, what?
Yota.
Hey, Minato. Good morning.
Good morning.
Good morning to you too, Koyun--
Yes! You're all here!
This isn't a dream, right?
We're all in the same class, right?
- You're not dreaming. Morning.
- Good morning.
Wait, this means you're...
Grade 2, Class 2, Number 2.
Meow, meow, meow.
Meow.
Since I'm Grade 2, Class 2, Number 22...
You're a meow, meow, meow, meow!
It's Azumi!
But Azumi...
isn't quite how I expected her to be.
It's great to meet you. I'm Miki.
You're... You're so cool.
SO COOL
THRILLED - SQUEEZE
Squeeze!
Good for you, Miki.
- I couldn't stop myself from hugging you.
- Azumi...
She's like a completely different person
from last year.
She was your hopes and dreams, huh?
Minato.
Can you do something about him?
Why am I the only one
in a different class?
GRADE 2, CLASS 1
Hayato's been whining all morning.
Wow.
- Thanks for everything, Hayato.
- You're so heartless!
SCREAM
What's your name?
I'm Tsukiko.
Tsukko then.
I'm Yota. Nice to meet you.
FLOATY
Floating away.
SIGH
It's, like, so lively in there.
It's going to be completely different
from Grade 1, Class 2.
Still, I don't hate it.
Koyun.
Sorry, we didn't mean to push you out.
Were we too loud?
Huh? Not at all.
Just thought there's no point
for me to be in there.
- What?
- Rather, sorry I made you worried.
This is difficult...
HE LOVES CROWDS
SHE LOVES SPACE
GRADE 2, CLASS 3
Is it okay to leave that person alone?
THAT PERSON
He likes to put on his loud comedy act.
A loud comedy act.
Listen...
I'm really glad we're in the same class.
Me too.
You feel more at ease
when there's a familiar face in class.
Right.
A FAMILIAR FACE
- Do you see that guy's hair?
- He's locked in.
Crap, what's my class again?
Second years are in charge
of club introduction skits, right?
Yeah.
I already know it'll be corny
so I don't want to participate.
I want to go watch it.
Seriously, don't come.
Hey!
SQUEEZE
Who is it?
This voice...
Yuki.
Bingo.
That's my Koyun.
Koyun?
You're the only one
who'd pull a prank like this.
They're friends?
That's fine,
but get your hand off her already.
Amamiya, meet Yuki.
He's Miki's younger brother.
What's up? I'm Yuki Azumi.
Huh? Miki's brother?
He's my younger brother.
We grew up together,
and he's her childhood friend.
Oh, I see.
Amamiya?
Could you be Minato?
- What?
- I totally know you.
Miki's mentioned your name before.
It's rude to point.
Thanks for being good to my sister.
Man, you're a solid 10!
- Wait, what?
- Oh, I know.
Are you guys in Miki's class?
GRADE 2, CLASS 2
STILL HANGING AROUND
Midorikawa, you're from Kansai?
I moved out here for high school.
I love Kansai dialect.
Do you actually?
I wanna say,
"What's up with that?" and stuff.
Your Kansai dialect's all messed up.
Miki!
Heya!
- What's up with that?
- You're using it.
Yuki!
I told you to leave me alone at school!
I'm gonna bother you anyway.
Anyway, here.
Your lunch. You forgot it again.
COMPLETE 180
Thanks, Yuki.
Be grateful.
You don't come to school together?
Nope. Yuki takes forever
getting ready, styling his hair and stuff.
Well, you know...
HMPH
Can't have people lookin' down on me.
You sound like a country bumpkin
delinquent. Knock it off!
- Yuki.
- Yeah?
Think you can make friends?
WHAT? EXPRESSION
FOR "YOU'RE ONE TO TALK"
There's someone I went to middle school
with in my class. I'm not worried.
Good for you.
It's like... she's more composed than usual.
RIGHT NOW - TALKING CASUALLY
USUAL - TIMID AND CAREFUL
She can talk to him
without feeling anxious.
Before I forget.
Come with me, Yuki.
Whoa!
What is it?
Yota.
This is Yuki. He's Miki's younger brother.
You're right. I see the resemblance.
You're massive!
I've heard of you, Yota.
Miki told me about you.
About me?
- Seriously, you're huge.
- Sheesh.
- Train rides must be comfortable.
- She doesn't need to introduce him.
Koyun said the same thing.
He can reach higher than the handrails.
Man, I'm jealous.
Those two...
share a special bond.
Meanwhile, I'm...
You feel more at ease
when there's a familiar face in class.
And she dated Igarashi in the past.
What am I going to do?
I wanted to be genuine friends,
I wanted her to smile...
But there's more to it than
these pure motivations now.
I wish she would only like me.
Hey, guys! Let's all sign up
for the sports festival's cheer squad.
CHEER SQUAD
RECRUITING MEMBERS
Why?
Last year, I passed on it,
then ended up regretting it on the day of.
I told myself I'd do it next time.
So what do you say, guys?
Okay, sure.
- Why not?
- Yes!
You'll join too, right, Minato?
Yeah.
I can't wait!
- A cheer squad full of friends!
- Amazing.
- This is the best!
- They agreed to that easily.
- Now, only one left is...
- That's Miki for you.
Koyun! We're gonna join
the cheer squad! Yeah!
I heard you.
It might be a lot of work, but good luck.
What?
LOOKY
BAM
Why me?
Sorry.
All right, first and second years.
If you haven't memorized
the first part, come over here.
SELF-PRACTICE TIME
Why's Hayato here?
Class 1 and 2 are in the same squad.
Act happy!
HERE
BLUE SQUAD - CLASS 1 AND 2
WINGING IT
Go swoosh, swoosh, then boom.
Koyun.
Want me to teach you
the parts you don't know?
GASP
A scary guy came over!
- Don't be afraid.
- What?
Meet Yuki, Miki's younger brother.
Good to meet ya!
PHEW
- Oh, I see.
- Don't introduce him.
Shoo! Off you go.
Why?
- Just go!
- She's scaring me.
Help me, Koyun.
Don't fight, you two.
Guess I've gotta leave now.
Now start walking!
Bye!
See you, Yuki.
POKE
Practice ended earlier than we thought.
Your finger...
GEEZ
I just exercised, so my face is sweaty.
That's what makes you upset?
STARE
- Do you have club activities after this?
- Yeah.
You've got cheer squad
and your club? That's tough.
Not really.
What's this?
Is this what I think it is?
Could this be...
Am I third-wheeling?
SWISH
Are you in a club, Shimojima?
JOLT!
He's talking to me now!
I-I'm in art club.
Were you in the cheer squad last year?
It's fine, Amamiya.
You don't have to include me.
I talked her into it.
- What should I do?
- How do you two know each other?
- I'd hate to be a third wheel...
- Last year, in March...
...but I do want to keep watching.
CURIOSITY - BEING CONSIDERATE
HEE, HEE
Goodness. I'm so done with practice!
I'm wiped.
It's only the first day.
Try to be more like
the energetic kids chatting over there.
CHATTER, CHATTER
You mean the first years?
Yeah, lots of flashy kids this year.
NEAR-SIGHTED
What's goin' on with Meiten?
This isn't our usual cohort.
That reminds me.
Earlier, I spotted two flashy students
who looked like celebrities.
- Seriously? Where?
- Right there.
NEAR-SIGHTED
See them?
The tall one with the bun
and the one with long hair.
Practice is done.
What're you gonna do, Akine?
Are you going home?
Not quite.
Momoka, you go home without me.
There's someone I want to meet.
See you.
Does the library ever get busy?
Not really.
That girl... she's staring right at us.
Heya.
- You stopped by about the manager role.
- Yes.
I guess she's
an acquaintance of Amamiya's.
Will you be coming after this today?
Yes. I look forward to seeing you there.
Koyuki Yuishiro.
Yuishiro?
Huh? Atagawa, do you know Hikawa?
Atagawa...
Yes.
I'm Akine Atagawa.
I'm from the same middle school as Azumi.
I heard all about you, Koyuki.
Akine Atagawa...
She can't be...
I look forward to getting to know you.
She's Manatsu Atagawa's...
younger sister...
Subtitle translation by: Megumi Hunter